You just said
you have a way to help me find the Liangshan assassin.
Tell me more about it.
Miss.
Bad news, Miss.
The Imperial City Department has surrounded the Zhao residence.
There are guards at both the front and back doors.
It's a huge formation.
What?
They must have tracked me down
and implicated the Zhao family.
Don't panic, sister.
The Zhao Manor,
no matter how fallen it is,
won't allow the Huangchengsi to easily break in with troops,
let alone search this backyard.
Don't worry, everyone.
Zhu'er,
come with me to take a look.
The Huangchengsi has received a report
that the Zhao Manor is hiding a rebel.
If you do not hand them over voluntarily,
we will immediately attack and search the manor.
I wonder
which official from the Capital Security Office you are.
Please show the search warrant.
Deputy Commander of the Capital Security Office,
Cui Hong.
By Chancellor Cai's verbal order,
I am here to arrest the rebel Chu Sanniang.
If you obstruct me again,
don't blame me for showing no mercy.
My Zhao family
may not have been involved in politics in the capital for years.
However, my uncle Zhao Mingcheng
has received an edict to return to service,
and is heading to Dongjing.
He will soon
take up his post.
My aunt, Li Qingzhao,
is highly talented
and greatly appreciated by His Majesty.
Her fame is renowned in court and among the people,
often discussing poetry with Madam Li and His Majesty.
Let me ask you,
can you bear the consequences
of trespassing on our estate,
Lord Cui?
Miss Zhao,
don't push your luck.
The rebel Chu Sanniang entered the Zhao estate through the back door.
The evidence is conclusive.
I am acting according to the law.
Even if the superiors find out,
I have nothing to fear.
Then, My Lord,
you can try.
What a stubborn and fierce young lady.
I won't barge in.
But ask the rebel Chu Sanniang
to come out and surrender obediently.
Lord Chu,
if you don't show yourself,
don't blame me for not saving you face.
How dare you!
This young lady has no official rank.
For obstructing the Imperial City Bureau,
even if I shoot her dead,
I am acting according to the law.
Commander,
think carefully.
My Lord,
don't be impulsive.
Put the big picture first.
Lord Chu,
I'll count to three.
If you don't come out,
I will shoot.
My lord.
How dare you!
Lord Cui.
I didn't know you were coming, Inspector Zhou.
Forgive me for not welcoming you properly.
Inside this sedan chair
is Li Yi'an,
the Householder of Yi'an.
His Majesty ordered me
to specially escort Householder Li
to the Zhao residence.
How dare you make trouble here?
My lord.
Please don't be impulsive, my lord.
Calm down, Madam Chu.
Lord Zhou You
has escorted Householder Li back.
It's all right now.
I was reckless
and offended Householder Li
and offended
Inspector Zhou.
Then get out of here!
Go.
Aunt.
Han.
About His Majesty's arranged marriage,
I know.
Your uncle has wronged you.
Please don't say that, Aunt.
I know I have been ill for a long time.
Now,
with this sick body,
if I can still help Uncle and the Zhao family,
it is my blessing.
You shouldn't stay at the Zhao family for too long.
During the Lantern Festival,
you can accompany me
to Fanlou
to relax.
Aunt,
do you have another appointment with Madam Li?
Shishi has composed a new tune
for Rumengling.
She will present it to His Majesty on the night of the festival.
Before that,
she invited me to appreciate it first.
Han'er's talent
is also outstanding.
So come along with your aunt.
Yes.
Sister, come here.
This is His Majesty's handwriting.
This is my handwriting.
If I hadn't seen you write it yourself,
I would have thought I wrote it.
Since the thief framed you with a letter,
why don't we give him a taste
of his own medicine?
Sister,
just let me see Liang Shicheng's handwriting.
That's not hard.
After dark,
I'll sneak into Liang Shicheng's mansion
and get a piece of his handwriting.
Rather than you risking stealing the letter, sister,
it's better
to seek Zhou You's help.
Zhou You is in the Palace Domestic Service.
It would be easier for him to get Liang Shicheng's handwriting
than for you to act rashly.
Besides,
we can use this to test his intentions.
Brother Meng.
How to find that Liangshan assassin,
please tell us in detail.
The mission Liangshan received
was to ruin the Knife Peddlers' business.
And the Knife Peddlers' business
is on the Bian River,
using modified merchant ships
to secretly transport smuggled salt and women for profit.
The latest ship.
It will arrive tonight at the hour of Xu
at Xishuimen Pier.
After the ship docks,
the smuggled salt and women
will be gathered at
the nearest tavern to the pier,
Yunxiang Tavern.
Liangshan only needs to expose this illegal trade
to complete the mission.
What will they do then?
These people from Liangshan are in Tokyo for the first time.
They are unfamiliar with the place.
But they have manpower,
so it is highly likely
that they will try to destroy the ships directly.
According to the request of the Master of Wuyou Cave,
the illegal trade must be exposed and blown out of proportion.
But the patrols on the Bian River are very strict.
If the navy controls the information on the ships
and prevents it from spreading,
then even if Liangshan destroys the ships,
they won't have completed the mission.
There is only one way left.
Attack Yunxiang Pavilion directly.
Based on what you said,
as long as we guard Yunxiang Pavilion,
we can ambush and capture them.
Meng,
do you still have any concerns?
The Master of Wuyou Cave wants to ruin the business of the Knife Lender.
Even if it's for his own profit,
it's a great deed
for the common people.
Meng,
do you want to
help Liangshan
complete this mission?
Catching the thieves and getting rid of the evil for the people at the same time.
Isn't it the best of both worlds?
Then,
what do you want to do?
We'll do as the Master of Wuyou Cave said,
and expose the Knife Lender's shady deals.